Contact

steelebrs@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bethsteele-865979121 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Management Hospitals

Beth Steele

VP of Operations and CNO OhioHealth Grant Medical Center: Providing operational and nursing leadership

Columbus, Ohio Area

Summary

I am a positive transformational nurse leader with extensive progressive leadership in operations and with experience in population health. I have a passion for leading with courage and vulnerability to build teams that support the health of those we serve well into the future.

I have experience in leading large-scale strategic initiatives to drive quality care, service, associate and provider engagement, growth, and value optimization within complex clinical and operational settings. I am a compelling influencer with an intense focus on building positive physician relationships, continuous improvement, revenue and productivity enhancement. Relationship building, strategic planning, collaboration, and reengineering with the ability to initiate positive transformational change are my key strengths.

Experience

OhioHealth

1 year 11 months

Vice President Operations and CNO December 2019 - Present (8 months)

Columbus, Ohio Area

VP of operations and chief nurse for Columbus, Ohio Level I Trauma Center and Magnet designated hospital.

Vice President of Care Management
September 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 4 months)
System Support

Enterprise wide leader for care management in population health.

Riverside Methodist Hospital

4 years 3 months

Vice President

August 2015 - August 2018 (3 years 1 month)

Columbus, Ohio Area

Vice President of Surgical Services and Oncology

Director of Surgical Services
June 2014 - August 2015 (1 year 3 months)

Atrium Medical Center
Director of Surgical Services
January 2012 - June 2014 (2 years 6 months)
Middletown, Ohio

Miami Valley Hospital 4 years 8 months Nurse manager March 2010 - January 2012 (1 year 11 months) Dayton, Ohio

Project Manager June 2007 - February 2010 (2 years 9 months) Dayton, Ohio Area

Education

Wright State University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2016)

University of Phoenix
Master of Science (M.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse